const Judiciary = [

	{
		questionText: 'Original Judistriction of Supreme Court',
		ans: ['A.131'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Appealent Judistriction of Supreme Court',
		ans: ['A.132, A.133, A.134, 134(a)-H.C issues, 136'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.136S',
		ans: ['pecial Leave Petition'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.137',
		ans: ['Review Jusdistriction of its Judjements, order'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.141',
		ans: ['SC desicions arre binding on lower courts'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.142',
		ans: ['Complete Justice'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.144',
		ans: ['Civil and judicial Authorites should act for sc'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.129',
		ans: ['Court of recorrds and contempt of the court'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.130',
		ans: ['Seat of the SC'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '124',
		ans: ['there shall be sc, Qualification, Appointment, Removal'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.125',
		ans: ['Salaries of sc'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.126',
		ans: ['office of the cji vacant then president appoints one of the other judges of the court'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.127',
		ans: ['Appoint of Ad hoc Judjes in sc'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.128',
		ans: ['Appointment of retaired Judges'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'No sc judge after retairment can become judge of any court',
		ans: ['A.124(7)'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.145',
		ans: ['power of sc to decide schedule, bench, holidays..'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.214',
		ans: ['There shall be HC of each state'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.213',
		ans: ['President has power to establish a common H.C'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.215',
		ans: ['HCs Court of Record and contempt of court'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.216',
		ans: ['H.C shall consists of CJH and the other judges as president may time to time deemped it nessary'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.217',
		ans: ['Appointment of Judges of HC'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.221',
		ans: ['Salaries of Hc..'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.223',
		ans: ['Appointment of Acting Judges in H.C'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.224',
		ans: ['Appointment of adittional and Acting Judge'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.230',
		ans: ['Power of a parliament to extend and remove judistriction of HC from any UT'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.225',
		ans: ['HC to make own rules cases, calender', 'In criminal case transfer petition'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.228',
		ans: ['Power of a HC to transfer a case to it'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Power of a SC to transfer a case to it',
		ans: ['139-A'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.222',
		ans: ['Transfer of HC judges from one HC to another by president on consultating by cji'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.220',
		ans: ['Restriction of practicing after being a perminant Judge'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.233',
		ans: ['Appointment of district judges '],
	},

];

export default Judiciary;
